Anand Murti

Portfolio: anandmurti.onrender.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anand-murti-61139945/

Overview & Vision

Ph: <u>+91 7070100897</u>

Hello recruiters, I have worked in various fields, such as design engineer as Mechanical Engineer, Technical support executive, software tester. But now I'm looking forward to developing my career as a Full Stack Web Developer. I have worked in live projects using MERN technology and I'm devoted to offer best of me along with enhancing my skills.

Hands on With: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, MongoDB, HTML CSS, NodeJS, ExpressJS

Friendly With: C++, JAVA

Work
Experience

2023-2024 LearnAt Edtech Private Limited

Role: Trainee & Web Developer Intern

Projects: Hotel Management, Clink, Website Maintenance

2022-2023 **ASTPL, Kolkata**

Job Role: Software Testing & Technical Support Exec.

CoreMacasia Technologies Pvt Ltd

2020-2022 **Job Role:** Technical Support Executive

2017-2020 ASHINA Systems

Job Role: Design Engineer

Education	&
Degree	

2013-2017 B.Tech Mechanical Engineering

Rawal Institute of Engineering & Technology, Faridabad

2012 Intermediate - BSEB 2012

2010 Matriculation – CBSE 2010

Skills

Coding:

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- HTML, CSS
- MERN Mongo, Express, React, NodeJS
- Redux
- GitHub

Others

- Solid Works (Machine Design Software)
- CATIA (Machine Design Software)
- AutoCAD (2D + 3D)
- Adobe Photoshop, Premiere
- MS Office

Certification

MERN Stack

Coding:

March 2023 – October 2023 LearnAt Edtech Private Limited

Internship:

Full Stack Web Developer Intern

November 2023 – February 2024 LearnAt Edtech Private Limited
